Itadori-kun, why is his nose bleeding?
Huh? I punched him.
When?
At the start of our fight.
Did his hand touch you?
Yeah.
My attacks won't work on him.
Huh?!
What?! Why?!
I'll explain while I'm lecturing you.
One, his technique doesn't
work on Itadori-kun,
or two, there's some reason
he won't kill Itadori-kun.
Either way, that's good for us.
However, I can halt his movements.
Once we've both created an opening,
we'll shower him with blows.
We'll make sure to exorcise him here.
Yeah!
I'll keep an eye on Itadori Yuuji...
while I start by taking
care of the 7:3 sorcerer.
I thought this would be a good one.
But they just dodged it.
And after dodging it, they started
shaving away the weaker ends.
It's only good for small fry.
Time to stop.
Right before he changes shape...
...he stores up cursed energy.
Good.
Even though I've made myself smaller,
there's still the risk of Itadori
Yuuji killing me in one blow.
He really is my natural enemy.
I'll need to make him behave for a bit.
Transfigured humans!
He still had a stockpile of them?
Kill the short-haired brat.
I knew it.
He can't kill humans!
Let's play!
Please...
kill me...
Next, I'll have him attack you, too.
I wonder if he'll cry then.
He's a foolish brat who can't
reconcile reality and his ideals.
You're wrong.
He's right in the middle of
making that reconciliation.
If it were up to me,
I'd say you're the fool.
Did you kill them?!
They know my tricks now.
I'm changing shape right
before the moment of impact.
I don't have time to create a substitute.
Ah, what...
what fresh inspiration this is!
Is this...
Death
death?
I bet I could do it now.
Domain Expansion:
Self-Embodiment of Perfection!
Shit.
Right now, I'm just...
grateful to you.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Episode 13:  Tomorrow
Quit screwing around!
Why did he only seal Nanamin inside?!
At this rate...
Domain Expansion.
Within an innate domain
constructed from cursed energy,
their ultimate technique
becomes one guaranteed to hit.
It's the height of jujutsu
sorcery I could never obtain.
Most likely, his cursed technique
requires touching the target
with his palm in its base state in
order to interfere with their soul.
However, in a domain that guarantees a hit,
that would mean I'm...
literally in the palm of his hand now.
Shit.
Jujutsu sorcerers are shit.
They have to be prepared to
cast away their lives for others,
and to occasionally force
their comrades to do so.
That's why I quit.
Or more like I ran away.
Do you like casse-croute?
Huh?
You always buy this one, don't you?
Oh, uh, yes.
They stopped selling it at
my local convenience store.
It's much better than a
convenience store's, isn't it?
Well, you are a bakery.
Wow, harsh.
Please come back again.
Fly head...
Leaving it alone won't hurt anything.
It'd be a bigger pain to deal with it and
have her think I'm some weird medium.
Hello, everybody!
You making those sales?!
When people trust us with their money,
they're trusting us with their lives.
So it goes without saying that we have to
balance the pursuit of profit against the risks.
There's no need to do
anything special at the start.
Just be sincere with the clients.
Never forget that.
Right!
Nanami...
Don't be so prudish all the time.
You're scaring the virgin.
So, new boy, what you need to think about,
first and foremost, are the company's profits.
They're directly connected
to our clients' profits, too!
Even when we con the client into buying
shitty stocks with no growth potential?
Of course!
It's suitable payment for us staring
at the markets around the clock.
Nanami, this is your second year, right?
You're clever. Let yourself run a bit more wild.
I have high expectations for you.
I'm someone with no concept of a "reason
for living" or "something worth doing."
I'll just earn a reasonable amount
of money by the time I'm 30 or 40,
and enjoy the rest of my aimless life
in a country with a low cost of living.
It's been four years since I left the school.
Whether I'm awake or asleep,
all I think about is money.
Curses and other people have nothing
to do with me as long I have money.
Money.
Money, money...
As long as I have money...
Are you all right?
Are you getting enough sleep?
What about you?
You look like your
fatigue's been building up.
Oh, you can tell?
Lately, it feels like there's
a weight on my shoulder.
I haven't been sleeping well, either.
My job is to take money from the wealthy
and make those people even more wealthy.
That's pretty much all it is.
Frankly, no one would mind if I was gone.
People who wanted to eat bread
would mind if their bakery was gone.
Yet for some reason, my job, which exists
outside that natural human cycle, pays better.
When you think about it
logically, it makes no sense.
A-Are you bragging?
No, I'm not.
Sorry, that was a bit complicated for me.
Could you take a step forward, please?
Huh?
How's your shoulder now?
Huh? Well...
Huh?! It's lighter!
If anything still feels off,
please go to the hospital.
Please excuse me.
Hey, wait!
Hold on!
Um...
Thank you!
Please come back again!
"Thank you."
Huh? Didn't you hear me? Thank you!
Please! Come back! Again!
Gojou Satoru
I always thought I was a person with
no concept of a "reason for living."
Hello, it's Nanami. I need to talk to you.
Yes, I'll be stopping by Jujutsu Tech tomorrow...
Why are you laughing?
Idle Transfiguration.
I'm grateful to you.
I don't need your gratitude.
I've already received it from lots of others.
I have no regrets.
How was he able to get in?
That's right... The more resistant
the inside of the barrier is,
the weaker it is to attacks from outside.
Domains are barriers specialized
in trapping something inside,
so they're actually easy to invade...
because there's no merit in doing so.
With Domains like Infinite Void and
Self-Embodiment of Perfection,
which guarantee victory, once they've ensnared
their target, that's even more true.
However,
inside Itadori-kun,
there lies something that must not be touched.
I warned you...
that there wouldn't be a second time.
There is no one in this world
more proud and conceited.
He lives guided by only his
pleasure and displeasure.
Whether you die...
or you die...
doesn't matter.
Aside from him,
I truly don't care.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
What just happened?
I'll kill you!
Domain Expansion...
That really burns cursed energy.
It truly is a trump card. A final technique.
And that damn Sukuna just...
But this is the critical moment!
Squeeze it out!
The last of my cursed energy!
The target's huge.
The flow of cursed energy is calm.
There are no counters.
I can land my attack for certain.
This is my last chance.
I don't need any more tactics.
Divergent Fist!
Wh-What is this lack of feedback?
Bye-bye!
Hold up!
This was fun.
Ino-kun, the core has
escaped into the sewers.
Yes.
Please scour everything from my
current location to the southeast.
Even you could exorcise him right now.
Let's pursue him, too!
Itadori-kun!
Come on, body! Move!
You're going to kill that thing, aren't you?!
You're going to crush him... into a pulp...
Itadori-kun!
So that was the King of Curses,
Ryoumen Sukuna.
He should have less total cursed energy
than Jougo at this point in time, and yet...
That presence...
His soul's on a different level.
I'm certain of it.
Even if we're all wiped out,
so long as Sukuna is resurrected,
the age of curses will come.
Still, damn, this sucks.
Right now, I want nothing
more than to kill Itadori Yuuji!
It's so frustrating!
But whatever.
Unlike his body,
I can kill his soul over and over again.
How should I kill it next time?
You were told to rest, weren't you?
Is this my lecture?
I have no lecture to give to
the person who saved my life.
I saved you?
That patchwork's cursed technique
was interfering with the soul.
Since you invaded his domain,
he wound up touching Sukuna's soul.
I was saved because of that.
But I didn't swap with him.
Sukuna never came out. Our opponent went in.
Then it wasn't me who saved you.
It was just his whim.
Nanamin, I killed a person today.
People die. There's no stopping that.
So I wanted them to at
least have proper deaths.
That's what I thought.
So I was always thinking about how I could
keep that trigger from being pulled.
But...
after pulling that trigger myself,
I don't understand anymore.
What is a proper death?
I don't know what that is, either.
Even if good people dying in peace
and evil people being punished
with death is the proper way,
most of the people in this world
are neither good nor evil.
Death is the final destination for all of us,
but no one dies the same death.
Trying to guide all of them to their
proper end would surely be arduous.
I personally wouldn't recommend it.
But you'll still do it anyway, won't you?
Just don't end up dying
yourself in the process.
Just as I would've died today
if you hadn't been there,
you'll see there are plenty of people
yet to come that need you, too.
Because you're a jujutsu
sorcerer now, Itadori-kun.
Put it in this box once you've filled it out.
And you don't need to write your name.
Survey on Bullying
Q1: Have you been bullied this school year?
A: I have been bullied. B: I have not been bullied.
Q2: Who have you been bullied by? Please circle all that apply.
A: Peers (people in your class)
B: Peers (people outside your class) C: Upperclassmen
D: Underclassmen E: Students from other schools
F: Other (                            )
Q3: What kind of bullying have you faced? Please circle all that apply.
A: Teasing, insults, slander
B: Ostracized, ignored by groups
C: Punched, kicked, beaten
D: Money or possession stolen
E: Possessions disturbed, soiled, or broken
F: Forced to do embarrassing
or unpleasant acts
G: Insults and scribbles were
drawn in your textbooks or notebooks
You're the one who gave Yoshino
those scars, aren't you, Itou?
I don't want hear any bitching from the guy
who was too scared to do anything at the time.
He quit school and moved away, didn't he?
So who cares?
What about me?
I've barely been able to move
my left arm since that day.
We're talking about your crimes right now.
Reflect on the punishment
you earned by yourself.
And where's your punishment?
Mine is yet to come.
First, I need to take a proper
look at the things I couldn't see.
Both you...
and I...
will have to bear the crime of killing
Yoshino's heart for the rest of our lives.
I'll be watching you, Itou.
I don't understand what a proper death is.
So at least...
until I do understand,
until I kill him,
I won't...
lose again.
Juju Stroll
Tuna.
Is it ready yet?
Salmon, salmon.
These meatballs are great.
Who made them?
Oh, I did.
They're easy to make.
1) Put all the ingredients in. Use twice as much ginger.
2) Mix together well and knead it.
3) Shape with spoons and toss into the pot.
Ingredients
Ground chicken
Finely chopped green onions
Ginger paste
Egg yolks (you can use the whites, too, if it's too much hassle)
Salt and pepper
Bonito flakes.
You can cook for yourself?
Not really surprising, actually.
No, Itadori taught me how to make these.
I see.
Itadori's legacy.
I don't think that's right.
These meatballs are great.
Oh, those are super easy to make.
Even Fushiguro can make them.
I taught him how.
I can't wait to see those two again.
Episode 14:
Kyoto Sister School Exchange Event - Group Battle 0 -